https://pbo.org/privacy/

Skip to navigation (Press Enter).
Skip to sub navigation (Press Enter).
Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Privacy Statement
Portland Baroque Orchestra is committed to honoring the privacy of visitors to our web site, www.pbo.org . This privacy policy governs any personal and business information collected from visitors to the Portland Baroque Orchestra web site. Our goal is to protect online information with the same diligence that we protect information obtained through other means.
Information Collection and Use
Portland Baroque Orchestra is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Portland Baroque Orchestra collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
Cookies
Portland Baroque Orchestra uses cookies to remember if users have logged in while on our site. This allows web site users to avoid logging in more than once, thereby saving time. Users have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on their browsers*. If users opt to disable cookies, they will still be able to use our Web site. However, they will not be able to use some functionality. No personally identifiable information (e-mail address, name, etc.) is collected with the cookies that we set. Accepting cookies while on the Portland Baroque Orchestra site will not put the user at risk for marketing to other sites.
*Different browsers have different cookie settings. With Netscape, you can ask the browser to allow, warn you, or completely disable cookies. Internet Explorer has an additional feature where you can specify different settings for different security zones. You can choose to allow Web sites to create cookies for you in your “trusted sites” (like Portland Baroque Orchestra), to warn you before you create them in your local Intranet zone, and to give you an option to never allow them in a “restricted zone.” See the “Help” section of your particular browser for more information on working with cookies.
Web Statistics
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use for reporting and sponsorship purposes. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners, sponsors, and donors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We only share this information so that we can secure funding to continue providing this site free of charge.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Portland Baroque Orchestra does not claim any responsibility for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information, and we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Surveys
Occasionally, our site requests information from users via Web surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include demographic data (such as zip code and age), but nothing that can identify any individual person will be collected unless the user opts to disclose such information. Survey results will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Send This to a Friend
If users elect to use our “Send This to a Friend” function, we ask them for the friend’s name and e-mail address. Portland Baroque Orchestra will automatically send friends a one-time e-mail message inviting them to visit the site. Portland Baroque Orchestra stores this information temporarily for the sole purpose of sending this one-time message.
Updates
We may also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements that contain important information about the service. We communicate with users to provide requested services and to discuss issues relating to their accounts via e-mail or phone.
Choice/Opt-in
Our users are given the opportunity to “opt in” to newsletters and site update e-mail messages. You may remove your own email address from our email-lists by clicking on the opt-out links provided in our automated bulk e-mail.  You may also send email-list removal requests to: info@pbo.org.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Privacy Statement
Print
Portland Baroque Orchestra is committed to honoring the privacy of visitors to our web site, www.pbo.org . This privacy policy governs any personal and business information collected from visitors to the Portland Baroque Orchestra web site. Our goal is to protect online information with the same diligence that we protect information obtained through other means.
Information Collection and Use
Portland Baroque Orchestra is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Portland Baroque Orchestra collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
Cookies
Portland Baroque Orchestra uses cookies to remember if users have logged in while on our site. This allows web site users to avoid logging in more than once, thereby saving time. Users have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on their browsers*. If users opt to disable cookies, they will still be able to use our Web site. However, they will not be able to use some functionality. No personally identifiable information (e-mail address, name, etc.) is collected with the cookies that we set. Accepting cookies while on the Portland Baroque Orchestra site will not put the user at risk for marketing to other sites.
*Different browsers have different cookie settings. With Netscape, you can ask the browser to allow, warn you, or completely disable cookies. Internet Explorer has an additional feature where you can specify different settings for different security zones. You can choose to allow Web sites to create cookies for you in your “trusted sites” (like Portland Baroque Orchestra), to warn you before you create them in your local Intranet zone, and to give you an option to never allow them in a “restricted zone.” See the “Help” section of your particular browser for more information on working with cookies.
Web Statistics
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use for reporting and sponsorship purposes. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners, sponsors, and donors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We only share this information so that we can secure funding to continue providing this site free of charge.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Portland Baroque Orchestra does not claim any responsibility for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information, and we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Surveys
Occasionally, our site requests information from users via Web surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include demographic data (such as zip code and age), but nothing that can identify any individual person will be collected unless the user opts to disclose such information. Survey results will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Send This to a Friend
If users elect to use our “Send This to a Friend” function, we ask them for the friend’s name and e-mail address. Portland Baroque Orchestra will automatically send friends a one-time e-mail message inviting them to visit the site. Portland Baroque Orchestra stores this information temporarily for the sole purpose of sending this one-time message.
Updates
We may also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements that contain important information about the service. We communicate with users to provide requested services and to discuss issues relating to their accounts via e-mail or phone.
Choice/Opt-in
Our users are given the opportunity to “opt in” to newsletters and site update e-mail messages. You may remove your own email address from our email-lists by clicking on the opt-out links provided in our automated bulk e-mail.  You may also send email-list removal requests to: info@pbo.org.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Buy Tickets
Donate
E-News Sign Up
E-News Sign Up
·required fields
·Email Address:
·First Name:
·Last Name:
Mailing Address:
City:
State/Province:
Zip/Postal Code:
Country:
USAAaland IslandsAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua And BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuracaoCyprusCzech RepublicDemocratic Republic of the CongoDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJersey
(Channel Islands)JordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinePanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRepublic of KosovoReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoa (Independent)San MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks & Caicos IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City State (Holy See)VenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Western SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Phone:
Close Window
